

Jacqueline Jumaga
FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

#### Contact

j.jumaga@gmail.com +33 (0)6 76 10 26 28 Paris, France

## **Skills**

JavaScript | React.js

Express.js | MongoDB

Mongoose | Node.js | Axios

HTML | CSS | Git

GitHub | Postman

**Project and Team Management** 

**Product Marketing** 

**Event planning** 

## Languages

English (maternal)
French (fluent)

# **Summary**

I am a recent graduate of IronHack Paris' web development boot camp seeking a solutions engineer role to continue my professional development. My experience includes full stack development with JavaScript, Express.js, React.js, Node.js, and MongoDB. In addition to my technical skills, I bring with me 13 years experience in management and client relations.

# **Education**

### 2021 Ironhack, Paris - Web Development Bootcamp, BAC +4

- Built full stack project using Express.js, Node.js, MongoDB and Axios
- Built single page application using React.js

2017 Alliance Française, Paris - Full time french language school

2013 - 2015 Mount Royal University - Event Management Program, BAC +3

2011 Sir Winston Churchill High School - Canadian Baccalaureate

# **Work Experience**

## Store Manager, Lululemon Athletica 2011 – 2020 Paris, France and Calgary, Canada

>In Paris, France (Nov 2017 - Nov 2020), Store Manager > In Calgary, Canada (Oct 2011 - Jan 2017), Product Manager

- Management of teams from 6 90 employees 5 years experience
- Training manager 5 years experience
  - Developed Europe wide training and coaching program in collaboration with other European training managers
- Visual merchandising 9 years experience
- Stock and delivery management 9 years experience
  - Led implementation of new inventory system, increasing on-hand inventory accuracy by 30%

## Entrepreneur Wedding Planner, Luna Events 2013 - 2017 Calgary, Canada

- Custom planning and execution of custom weddings in Calgary and the Canadian Rocky Mountains between 100-300 people
- Strong marketing strategy 23 weddings planned and executed in first 2 vears of business
- Strong connection with over 40 local vendors

# **Awards and Volunteer Experience**

### Sous Chef @ S.A.L.T.S., Victoria Canada 2010 - 2015

 2nd in cuisine on a tall ship summer camp for kids and young adults, preparing 4 meals a day for 40 people over 10 days

### Duke of Edinburgh Award, Gold level 2011

• Founded by Prince Philip, Duke of Edinburgh, recognizes young adults for their achievements in personal development.